Good morning.
It has been a long time.
Nice to meet you.
You're doing great.
I'm glad to be taking pictures once again.
Once again, we are Battention itself.
I am Kyamai.
I am Sakura Seta. Pleased to meet you.
Now, for the answer.
I'm a little embarrassed to answer.
Why?
Hinata Bell.
Hinata Bell, yes.
I'm in Miyazaki.
Yes.
This is all of Kyushu?
That's right.
We had said that we would shoot our music video in all prefectures in Kyushu,
Finally, we came to Miyazaki for the last time.
What a great location!
This was very much there, I wanted to come to Miyazaki.
It's my first Christmas song.
Yes, it is.
We.
But something,
I don't know, I like the fact that it's not too Christmasy.
It's nice, the weather.
I've heard a rumor here and there,
Rumor has it that we're going to be photographed the cutest today.
Cutest?
I hope so. I hope they take a cute picture of me.
If they take cute pictures.
Well, I mean, when they're in the jacket jacket.
The time of the jacket?
Did something happen?
What's going on?
Well, the manager told me..,
I was told by the manager that he was confident that Miu looked the best in this outfit,
That's not true at all,
I'll do my best to look as cute as possible in the music video.
I think the director likes it.
Yes, I think so.
That's right, he asked me if it was cute.
Yes, he asked if it was cute,
He said it was cute, so at that time.
I wonder if he will take another cute picture.
Good morning.
You came to Miyazaki, didn't you?
I'm here in Miyazaki.
Tomorrow, I don't know if it's Akita, but something suddenly came up.
Now.
Miyazaki is here, isn't it?
Golf, it wasn't golf.
It was a drone.
A drone.
I want to play golf.
I wonder if they have a little golf air or something just for Lira.
I like Lilla Golf Air.
I always look at it and think it's cute.
I want one.
I heard that Arline, a senior, said she started golfing because she wanted to wear a Golf Air.
I see. Maybe I'll start playing golf with Lila.
You know, the one that says "Nice.
What's nice? Fah!
FAR!
But you say it when you hit it too far or OB, so it's a bit of a failure.
Failure. Nice!
FAR!
That's a lillafarceau.
It's more like...
Faso.
What did you enjoy most about the music video?
Well, this time...
It's a bit like Christmas.
I think it's a bit like a party.
I think there's a bit of a party atmosphere.
But this place is very tropical.
So...
I'm really looking forward to seeing how it's going to turn out.
Also, I heard that there are golf and fishing facilities.
I'm going to try something I've never done before.
So I'm very excited.
Is there such a thing as an interview?
Hiding in plain sight.
This is Hinataville's first batten show. What's your first Christmas song?
A Christmas song.
We've always wanted to do a Christmas song or a winter song.
We've always wanted to do a Christmas song or a winter song, so we decided to do a Christmas song set in Hyuga, Miyazaki prefecture in Japan.
So this Christmas song is set in Hyuga Miyazaki prefecture in Japan, so I think it shows our character.
I think it's a Christmas song set in Miyazaki prefecture in Japan, so I think it really shows our character.
But there's also that sparkling Christmas feeling, and the fact that it's set in Miyazaki.
The song is set in Miyazaki, so I think the lyrics are filled with it.
I'd like people to pay attention to the fusion of the two.
Also, the lyrics were written by a teenage rapper named Anatsume, who is a lot younger than me and I am.
And the lyrics were written by Anatsume, a rapper in his teens who is a lot younger than I am.
I think it's filled with the Christmas of the 1950s.
I think it's because it's filled with the Christmas of our generation.
I think that's why the Christmas of the 1950s is so packed in there.
There are a lot of things like that, aren't there?
I hope you'll pay attention to that this time.
And Mie-chan's solar is amazing.
Yes, and after that...
She has a beautiful voice.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
But then Riko comes in.
She takes it to the next level.
Please pay attention.
Pay attention!
Cute!
Yes, it is.
I've always wanted to wear a Christmas costume. I had an image of our seniors wearing them.
I think I like this one better.
It's more like a batten show.
What's the image? Ethnic?
Some kind of ethnic group.
This time it's a tropical Christmas.
I think it's a tropical Christmas, and the blue is the first thing that comes to mind.
I don't know, it's kind of South American.
There are a lot of patterns like a faisley pattern in various places.
The material of the costume is fresh.
And these feet... What are they called?
Leg warmers?
I don't know what to call them.
And on the head...
And this brain hat on his head.
And the beads... each member's color...
And the overall silhouette is also different.
The upper body is a little different.
Some have ribbons, some have simple ribbons, some have sleeves.
And some have sleeves... each one is made separately.
Where's the sponge?
This is the one, isn't it?
I knew it! It's Kinna's specialty.
Moe!
I thought I could make it moe.
I thought it would be moe.
I didn't expect it to be sleeveless.
It's a revolutionary costume.
Yay!
Is this your first time wearing a hat?
Oh, sure.
It's the first time I've worn a hat this tight.
I've been wearing a tiny hat.
I don't know...
I've pulled it off before, but...
But this is the first time I've worn it like this.
But it's so much cuter
When you wear it like this...
It makes a big difference, doesn't it?
It's different when you don't have it on.
That's right.
It gives it a wintery look.
It's totally different when you wear it to make it look more wintery.
Right?
It plays a big part.
Yes, sir.
Yes, yes.
You've got no choice but to do it.
That's right.
And these are long sleeves.
All three of them are just the right shape now.
That's right.
They're different.
Cloth less type.
This one is cute.
Ribbon
This one's cute, isn't it?
It's cute.
It has ribbons.
The most.
They have the most fabric.
Try it here.
Oh, my God.
That's it.
It's just a little bit more airy.
I didn't paint this.
Oh, no.
Stop chilling!
Yes, Mii, you can cool off like this.
I'll get burned only here!
Oh no!
I wonder if I can get it off.
We've only done this once, right?
Oh, no.
Oh, man.
Is this the one time?
Yeah.
Twice.
Ding, ding, ding, ding.
Ding, dong, dong, dong.
I'm on a roll.
I'm on a roll
One tune, but...
Twice.
Twice
Ding, dong, dong, dong
Ding, dong, dong, dong, dong
Two times.
2 times
1 song
One song.
All right, let's go through.
I'm so excited.
I'm so excited, I can't wait to see what happens.
There it is.
Yesterday, right?
It's a better environment than the one at the festival.
The environment is great.
Yes, on the flat side, yes.
It's rare to have such a nice environment.
It's better than most.
It's a nice environment.
Yeah, it's nice.
I've seen this place at festivals.
Dancing in a place like this.
You can't see what's underneath.
There's grass down there.
I'll do the grass too
Up there
It's okay.
I don't know, this whole choreography is just so incredibly cute and choreographed.
The chorus is really easy to dance.
Everyone can imitate and dance along with it.
I think it's a dance that everyone can imitate and dance along with.
Yes, I think so.
Also, when you shake your head and ring the bell, it goes "kumkumkumkumkumkumkumkumkumkumkumkumkumkumkum".
It's so cute when it becomes a canon.
It's cute.
It's cute to look at, and it's cute to dance to.
And then there's the choreography that goes along with the lyrics.
And then there's the choreography that sounds like a bird in the sun according to the lyrics.
And there's also a choreography that makes it sound like they're holding a package.
It's a cute choreography that matches the lyrics.
I hope you can imitate it at the live.
Is there anything you want people to imitate in the live performance?
I think the chorus.
The chorus
Wave your hands a lot
Wave your hands and then...
Kuru?
Kuru Kuru?
Ring the bell, please.
I'll ring it.
And you have three chances to ring it in 222.
You know, the one you're all asking for.
That's right.
He's going to match the treasure.
Please do it.
Please do it!
Yes, please!
And Christmas time... it's at the end of the chorus.
That's where the members get to know each other.
Yeah.
The choreography is a lot of fun.
I'm looking forward to it.
It's fun.
Yes, it is.
Come on, come on.
We're flying through the air
The light rings a bell
I'll fall in love with your heart
Well, this time I listened to Hinata Bell
I was also listening to the concept of the song.
I was listening to the concept of "Merry Christmas from Hinata".
I was listening to the song while listening to the concept.
It has a Christmas feeling to it.
The song has a Christmas feeling, but it also has a tropical feel to it.
I heard that it was inspired by the geography of South America.
I heard that the song was inspired by the geography of South America, and it has that kind of Christmas atmosphere.
The whole song has that kind of Christmas atmosphere, but for some reason, it's like it's wrapped in a southern breeze.
So the song has that kind of atmosphere.
There was also the concept of the song.
I wanted to create a mismatch between the two.
I wanted to take a lot of mismatched pictures to be released at Christmas time.
I wanted to shoot a lot of mismatched pictures to be released at Christmas time.
I wanted to shoot a lot of mismatched pictures for this music video.
Next time preview
It looks like we're going to play golf this time.
But I don't have any experience in golf.
I wonder how it will turn out.
I hope it's beautiful.
I hope it won't be too tacky.
What's your image?
I'm thinking of Ai-chan.
Ai-chan is relatively all-powerful.
I have the image of her being able to do everything.
I have an image of her being able to do everything.
The rest of the members
The rest of the members are pretty lame.
Gatchi has golf clubs.
There's a club.
That's great.
Yay!
FAR.
FAR!
Nice.
Fur is everybody a little bit
Nice piece
Yes, ma'am.
Farr.
I'm in charge of Fur
In charge of Fur
Fur of Fur.
Yes, sir.
I didn't mean it like that at all.
Fur... Fur...
Fur. Fur.
Kichia.
Fur
Del Abigail
w
kun
un
Too much.
I thought nothing of it.
Yes, sir.
It's going up.
why why clicked
1Why are you going on?
Yes.
That means you're going to swing it around a lot.
It swings a lot.
Wow.
But, I'm going to take another swing.
What's that? Baseball?
Baseball.
Any reception?
It's crazy.
Oh! Congratulations!
If it's just the most mouthful, that's the reception.
Congrats!
You guys are so cool.
Okay, I'm on it.
Okay, roll the camera.
Oh, is this the real thing?
It's a production.
Go for it!
Cheer for me.
Yeah!
Go for it!
Here we go.
Oh!
We're moving on.
I don't get it.
Let's go!
Ready.
Ah!
What?
Ready.
Oh, no, no, no, no.
Se-no.
Yo!
Oh!
Oh, wow!
That's great!
It's so good.
Wow.
Here we go!
Aaah!
That's great.
Here we go!
Aah!
Oh, go!
Go!
Ooh!
Oh, my God!
Oh, my gosh!
Oh, no.
I'm ahead of you!
Too much!
Oh, man.
Oh!
It's gone!
Aah!
Shhh!
Amazing.
Holy shit.
Oh!
Huh!
That's a little dangerous.
Number 7. You're going in.
Go for it! Go for it!
Number 7. Yeah!
Yes!
Oh, like this, right?
Go for it! Oh!
Ooh!
Ready, go!
Se-no, pop!
Ooh!
Ooh! Oh, my gosh!
What? I want to do it.
Yo-koi.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
Four...
I'll get it for you.
сказel
car
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
I don't want it!
Then let's get someone in!
Who's good at this so far?
No one's answering!
Riko.
Well then, let's go Riko!
I'll do my best! It's so close!
If we can't get in, we're doomed!
Good luck!
Riko! Good luck!
May I?
I'm going in!
Okay!
Wait! Don't look!
Whoa!
That's crazy!
Sadness!
Last one! Yes!
Go!
Yeah!
How's it going?
Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
Boo-hoo!
That's great, that's great, that's great.
What's the big deal?
Feelings.
I'm sorry.
I think Leila was missing the feeling.
Yes, ma'am.
Go for it.
That's great.
Is it the feeling?
It's the feeling.
That's great.
That's amazing!
It's all about feeling, right?
You have to start from the beginning.
We shouldn't put on clothes.
You can't do it with clothes on
You should put on clothes
Put some clothes on!
Have you ever been fishing?
No, I've never fished.
Only at the fishing pond.
Fishing pond.
I've never seen a live fish.
Really? Like freshly caught.
Really?
What do you get?
This river.
You can't get anything like this.
Is it pre-fishing?
But, you know, at the end of the day, you get a present.
You'll catch a present?
We're going to do a skit called...
A Christmas present?
Yes, yes, yes.
It's light.
Light? Heavy?
Ehhhh...
It doesn't have a fishing spring.
So it's not dangerous?
Dinner tonight.
I'll try it.
I'm gonna try it.
What kind of fish is that?
And finally, some for us.
I want sashimi.
Here we go.
Oh, wow.
That's great.
Here we go!
Eeet!
Oh!
Oh! Cool!
I love it! But it's kinda cute!
I'm sure he'll see it floating around here and say, "Oh, you used it for something, didn't you? and take a picture of me making a fuss.
Oh, I think I lost.
May I? Pull.
Come on.
Come on. Come on.
Ah! Smoke!
I'm going!
What?
Tomosuke!
I don't get it!
Are you sure?
What?
Photographer!
Cameraman! Cameraman!
What?
What is that?
Did I hit your hand?
Aah!
What?
Why?
Did I hit your hand?
Something, something...
Around there?
But it looks like you're catching a lot of fish!
That's great!
I could make it look like I caught it!
But he also acted like he really caught something!
Really!
It really caught!
It really worked!
It looked like it was on!
It's Ai, just a little bit...
So, should I take a picture of you too?
Yes, sure.
Mr. Ai.
Scary, scary, scary!
Slowly...
Wow.
Oh, oh, oh...
Oh, perfect.
I can't tell.
I can't split.
Is it heavy?
It's heavy.
Okay, let's try it.
Even
Nó.
voodoo. We talked.
That was a little fast.
vaight
Oh, yeah!
Yes!
That's great!
Talking in a shaking Konami
And yes
Eye contact and go in.
Yes, side
I have a good thing for you.
Hang in there.
Go for it!
Oh лаг Dragon
I hate it
I hate it!
Woooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooo!
LOL
Ending
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
As it soars through the sky, the light rings a bell
Is that what it sounds like?
It's OK, right?
Okay!
Yes!
Okay, can I get a little closer shot of you catching the ice cream fan?
Can I take a step back and get a closer look?
I'm so embarrassed.
I'm behind the scenes.
No, I'm not.
Okay, hold on.
Okay, wait.
Okay, here I go!
Oh no!
Oh, no!
Oh, man!
Oh, my gosh!
OK!
LOL!
You did it perfectly! LOL!
Good morning!
I'll look for a place!
Thank you!
Good thing the weather is nice!
Somehow!
Good luck!
Around Miyazaki city sightseeing
This is the city hall
This is the Tourism Association
Thank you very much!
Once again, we
Patient Title!
Please take care of us!
Please appeal to Miyazaki!
Thank you very much!
Thank you!
A lot!
It's moai!
It's my first moai!
Face to face!
As you can see, the moai statues are lined up.
Moai statues and
Moai statues
together
Looking up at the sky
I'm feeling the wind of Miyazaki
Feeling the wind
I wanted to take a shot
Wish I could take a shot
Please wait for the camera!
Here we go!
Ready! Action!
Hold the camera!
Stand by for camera!
Please hold camera!
This.
It makes sense.
Ah, madrasah. Scholarship.
Finance.
Where we stood between earlier.
Work and health.
Health and love.
Finance and marriage.
That's great.
Yay.
Let's go.
Oh, wait.
Wait a minute.
I'll be quick.
I'm coming.
What's this?
What is this?
Well, then, this is it.
It's...
That's love.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah. I want more work.
Give me more gigs.
I chose "healthy" because it means I can work hard, play hard, and eat a lot of food.
I want to have a lot of love, and I want you to like me a lot.
I also want to improve my academic ability, so I chose "improve my academic ability".
I'd like to improve my academic ability, so I've decided to improve my academic ability.
I'll be happy if you'll give me a boost.
I'm sure you'll be happy to see it.
I said I'm glad we have it.
I want peace and cool dreams come true so anything can come true here Stamin I want it to come true
I want peace on earth, peace for all of us, peace for all of us, and smiles on our faces.
Peace for a long time and
I want to eat a sweet potato.
I can eat a sweet potato with peace of long time.
I got a sweet potato.
Now we're in the devil's choice.
I remember this place from the Drop Festival.
This is where we were at the Drop Festival.
I remember.
Hmm...
This is Aoshima Shrine.
Aoshima Shrine.
You went there, didn't you?
Wow, that's amazing.
To think this was created by nature...
I'm...
I'm amazed.
Did it come naturally?
I wash most of it over here.
It's in the back, where there's more detail.
You know, the grease and grime.
The devil...
It won't come off.
Laundry Aitor.
I've used it in home economics
I do it in elementary school
Mr. Furuta
Shall I wash your clothes?
Mine?
You didn't spill hot food with her, did you?
I'm fine.
There's no rice stains or anything.
You should all do some laundry.
Wash your mind.
Everyone's heart is clean.
That's right.
They're idols.
This time.
We're shooting in Miyazaki Prefecture.
If we're going to this trouble...
I thought it would be nice if we could experience Miyazaki together.
I wanted to make a video that would allow us to experience Miyazaki together.
I thought it would be great if we could make a video
In this case...
Park golf at the park.
Aoshima's devil's washboard.
or moving around with the members of the group.
I wanted to show the members in action.
Experiencing the experience.
with the members in a reality audio
with the reality audio
I think it would be great if we could express
I thought that the viewers could experience it with me
I thought it would be a good idea
I was thinking
I was thinking that we could make the most of it.
This time
I think there is a double meaning with Hinata Bell.
There is a scene where they eat chicken nanban.
Miyazaki's food and
and fun activities
and other fun activities
I think it's a double-meaning of the scene where the members experience
When you watch the video, you can see
Miyazaki is a place where you can experience
that you can experience in Miyazaki.
You can feel a part of the experience
I think you will be able to feel
I think the video will help you to feel a part of the experience
I hope you can feel
I hope you can feel the joy
I hope you can feel the joy of Miyazaki
I hope you can feel the joy of Miyazaki.
This is love.
Affection?
I don't need it.
Love is the best.
Love is the best?
No, I don't want it.
I don't need it.
It's pretty light.
It's light.
Is this how it's supposed to be?
We've finished shooting the music video for "The Sunshine Bells.
Thank you very much.
Thank you very much
This time it took 2 days
Over 2 days
How was it, Mi-chan?
It's a sparkling song.
Even in the shooting of the music video
We all sparkled together.
I really enjoyed the feeling of Christmas.
And the location in Miyazaki
It was so much fun!
Amazing!
It really feels like Miyazaki!
After the shoot
I really have this self-consciousness.
Except for you.
Except you.
Then I'm sure this Hinata Belle
I thought the music video
I thought it was full of highlights.
I hope you enjoy it.
I don't need it.
Thank you for watching until the end.